export const data = [
  {
    question: "Why are the Los Angeles Lakers called the Lakers?",
    option1: "They originally came from Minnesota, the 'Land of 10,000 Lakes'",
    option2: "Their first arena was on a lake",
    option3: "Their founder was named Lake",
    option4: "No one knows",
    ans: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "What is depicted on the logo of the Golden State Warriors?",
    option1: "A basketball",
    option2: "A bridge",
    option3: "A city skyline",
    option4: "A spearhead",
    ans: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Who was the shortest player to win a MVP?",
    option1: "Allen Iverson",
    option2: "Charles Barkley",
    option3: "Spud Webb",
    option4: "Steve Nash",
    ans: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "What was the 'process' of former 76ers general manager Sam Hinkie?",
    option1: "Looking for players in Europe",
    option2: "Only drafting excellent 3 point shooters",
    option3: "Signing veteran leaders",
    option4: "Tanking for serveral years in a row and getting high draft picks",
    ans: 4,
  },
  {
    question:
      "When Kevin Durant won the MVP award in 2014, he said someone else was 'da real MVP'. Who was it?",
    option1: "Barack Obama",
    option2: "His mom",
    option3: "LeBron James",
    option4: "Russell Westbrook",
    ans: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "What team used to be the Seattle Supersonics?",
    option1: "Sacramento Kings",
    option2: "Memphis Grizzlies",
    option3: "Oklahoma City Thunder",
    option4: "Detroit Pistons",
    ans: 3,
  },
  {
    question: "Who is the all-time NBA leader in assists?",
    option1: "Chris Paul",
    option2: "Jason Kidd",
    option3: "Magic Johnson",
    option4: "John Stockon",
    ans: 4,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Who scored eight points in the final 8.9 seconds to beat the New York Knicks in a 1994 playoff game?",
    option1: "Penny Hardaway",
    option2: "Grant Hill",
    option3: "Scottie Pippen",
    option4: "Reggie Miller",
    ans: 4,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which NBA legend was known as 'The Admiral' because of his Navy background?",
    option1: "John Havlicek",
    option2: "Gary Payton",
    option3: "David Robinson",
    option4: "Patrick Ewing",
    ans: 3,
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the record for most regular season wins, set by the Golden State Warriors in 2015-2016?",
    option1: "50",
    option2: "69",
    option3: "73",
    option4: "82",
    ans: 3,
  },
];
